http://www.cimaware.com/privacy

Legal
Website termsSecure orderingTerms of service (TOS)Money back guaranteePrivacyCookies policy
Recover a file
EN
EnglishEspañolDeutschItalianoFrançaisPortuguês
HomeLegalPrivacy
Privacy policyCimaware Software S.L., puts a priority on the protection of the personal data of its customers. We recommend reading the entire Privacy Policy and if you have any questions please contact us.
The handling of personal data complies with the regulation set out in Organic Law 15/1999 of 13 December on the Protection of Personal Data (Official State Journal of 14 Dec. 1999) (Spain).
Our web site facilitates the purchase of products and the lending of services via electronic forms that require the user to furnish certain information (mandatory personal information) essential for the provision of services as well as other optional personal information that the user may provide if he/she so desires. Once the user clicks on the request button, this data is transmitted, stored and processed in an automated data file.
Cimaware Software S.L. guarantees the confidentiality of the data file containing the personal information obtained via the website form. Personal data thus collected will never be passed on to third parties or entities in compliance with limits established under law.
Users shall at all times be able to exercise their rights of access, rectification, cancellation and opposition with regard to personal data provided communicating by means of standard post, e-mail or fax clearly indicating name, surname(s) and address. Cimaware Software S.L. contact information is found at the bottom of this document.
The user tacitly accepts the above-described processing of his/her personal data and guarantees that such data is truthful and accepts responsibility for communicating any change to Cimaware Software S.L..
The data files and web sites owned by Cimaware Software S.L. are hosted in servers located in the Netherlands and in Spain. The user tacitly accepts and provides consent for the transfer of his/her personal data to said servers in the Netherlands and Spain where the data shall be stored under conditions of the highest possible security (Article 34 of Organic Law 15/1999 of 13 December).
In order to protect customer privacy, the purchase of products is processed through a data channel with a 2048 bits TLS encryption key certified by the entity known as Sectigo Limited.
On occasion Cimaware Software S.L. uses cookies in its web page. If so desired, one may control the use of these cookies by configuring the navigator in such a way that it provides notification of their existence or automatically rejects them. It is however recommended that they be enabled for the smooth operation of all services.
Cimaware Software S.L. is not responsible for the privacy policy of web sites that do not belong to the company but which may be visited via links.
Cimaware Software, S.L.
C/ Santa María Magdalena 9
28016 Madrid, Spain
Software toolsAccessFIXExcelFIXWordFIXOutlookFIXOfficeFIXDeleteFIX Photo
CompanyAbout usContact us
UsersYour accountSupportBe a partnerResellerAffiliate
FAQOrderingPaymentContactEvaluationInstallationAccessFIXExcelFIXWordFIXOutlookFIXDeleteFIX Photo
BlogsACCDB Crash HelpExpert zoneExpert ZoneAccess articlesExcel articlesWord articlesOutlook articlesAuthors
WebsiteSite mapWebsite termsTerms of service (TOS)Cookies policyMoney back guaranteeSecure orderingPrivacy
Copyright ©2000-2020 Cimaware Software. All Rights Reserved. Microsoft, MS, Office, Excel, Word and Windows are either registered trademarks or trademarks of Microsoft Corporation in the United States and/or other countries.
This website uses cookies to manage sessions, forms, statistics and others. More information.
Accept | Refuse
